Laci Zeidler Software Developer

ABOUT ME

After working in retail and foodservice for 7 years, I knew that I wanted to pursue a career that challenged me mentally and creatively. Software development sparked my interest over three years ago and I finally found an institution that suited my needs as an aspiring software developer. I am always ready to learn new concepts and find myself getting excited to learn a new language or program.

CONTACT

618.318.6657

laci.zeidler@gmail.com

https://github.com/lacizeidler

 $\underline{https://www.linkedin.com/in/lacizeidler/}$

https://lacizeidler.github.io/laci_zeidler/

SKILLS

- Javascript
- React
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Git/GitHub

PROJECTS

Tim the Tool Man | Front End Capstone View Code

Tim the Tool Man is a home repair business application that allows people to submit requests to Tim for all different kinds of home repair projects. Tim can keep track of his list of clientele by clicking on a customer's name and that leads him to their profile with their active requests.

- This multiple-page app has full CRUD functionality and was created utilizing React, React Router, and API fetch calls to JSON server.
- App has different views for unregistered users, registered, users, and Tim.

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Nashville Software School | Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

Intensive, full-time 6-month software development program learning full-stack technologies through the creation of applications in the group and individual setting.

- Git and GitHub for version control
- Simulated agile work environment
- Experience in remote collaboration
- Created applications using diverse tech stacks including HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and React

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Store Associate

True Value | Aug 2020 - Jan 2021 Cashier at Kellermans Feed and Supply in my hometown of Pinckneyville, IL.

- Stocked products and managed inventory count using the RockSolid POS system
- Helped customers find products based on various projects that they need help with
- Responsible for counting the contents of the cash register drawer at the end of each shift, maintaining receipts, records, and withdrawals

Social Media Manager

True Value | Jan 2021 - Present

In charge of Kellerman's Feed and Supply online presence including Facebook, Instagram, and company website.

- Created Facebook and Instagram posts based on store sales, events, and featured products
- Created and updated the company website on Shopify
- Saved store \$300 a month on our online presence, a savings of over \$3600 over the past year

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School

Certificate, Software Development, Mar 25, 2022

Southeast Missouri State University

Bachelor of Science, Business Administration, Cum Laude